

I Putu Gede Agus Andika Putra iOS Developer

Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia (62) 82135923636 ipg.guska.p@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/andika-p-2a337a214/ https://github.com/gus-ka

# **SUMMARY**

I have been working as an Android developer since 2018, as an iOS developer since 2019 and as a Flutter developer since 2020. I have a good knowledge and experience in some program languages and techniques of Swift, Java, Kotlin, Dart, PHP, HTML, CSS, JS, SQL, XML. I love Test-driven development (TDD), I love solving problems by programming and crafting simple, elegant code and I love MVVM, VIPER as a design pattern.

# **EXPERIENCE**

Itsavirus, Bali, Indonesia - iOS Developer

February 2022 - Present

- Fixing bugs of existing an iOS project using Swift programing language and an Android project using Kotlin programing language
- Adding new features to an existing application
- TDD
- Unit Testing
- Participate in Daily Standup

PT. Appkey, Bali, Indonesia - Web Developer

November 2020 - February 2022

Fixing bugs of existing projects

PT. Appkey, Bali, Indonesia - Flutter Developer

Maret 2020 - February 2022

- Responsible for creating an Android Application and an iOS Application using the VisualStudioCode with Dart programing language
- Fixing bugs
- Adding new features to an existing application
- Launching Android Applications to AppStore and PlayStore

# PT. Appkey, Bali, Indonesia - iOS Developer

January 2019 - February 2022

- Responsible for creating an iOS Application using the XCode with Swift programing language
- Fixing bugs
- Adding new features to an existing application
- Launching Android Applications to AppStore

# PT. Appkey, Bali, Indonesia - Android Developer

Agustus 2018 - February 2022

- Responsible for creating an Android Application using the Android Studio with Java programing language
- Fixing bugs
- Adding new features to an existing application
- Launching Android Applications to PlayStore

# **EDUCATION**

Satya Wacana Christian University, Salatiga, Central Java - Bachelor's Degree

2013 - 2017

Information Technology

#### **SKILL**

Java

Swift

Dart

Kotlin

JavaScript

• HTML

• Cascading Style Shee

Android Developmen

• iOS Development

• Flutter Development